Here's the code for the Refresh button in
the forecastfragment menu XML file. We want it to
appear in the overflow menu, so we set showAsAction
as never. We also declare the string. You can
find the string here in the strings.xml file, which
is located in the values folder, which is in
the res folder. You can get your strings.xml file
translated into different languages. This adds additional values folders,
under Res. For example, you would have
values-es, for Spanish, values-fr for French. And
within each of those values folders, you
would have a strings.xml file, which would
contain the localized strings for that language.
Since translation does cost money, as a
pro tip, you can mark strings that
you don't need translated using translatable=false. For example,
if it's a proper name or if it's for debugging like this one,
then you can indicate to the translator that they can skip over this strings